Previously on Heated Rivalry...
-Where's your boy Rozanov?
-My what?
Scott Hunter is right next door.
-No, I mean, not in a...
-Not your boy.
Just, like, it's always
Hollander and Rozanov, right?
He is hot. We should let him
listen like mating call.
-He's an asshole, right?
-Yeah, basically.
The record for this event,
currently held by the New York
Admirals' Scott Hunter...
Glad Rozanov didn't hold my
record for more than a minute.
Nice shooting, rook.
-Thought it was Hunter's year.
-Babe!
-Can you believe Russia?
-Be nice, Vaughnny.
Hey, what did Roz say about it?
-I don't know.
-Nothing to me, that's for sure.
We're not, like, friends
or anything.
I'm sure someone else
grabbed him.
-It's USA this year, baby!
-We're coming for you. Trust me.
You look great
in silver, Vaughnny.
-Oh, good one.
-Oh!
Ha. I want some
ice cream bad, man.
Do you not find it weird
that we're in a beach town
in Russia in February,
talking about getting ice cream?
Winter Olympics, baby.
Just as it should be, right?
Hey, isn't... isn't that...
Oh, yeah.
-Hollander!
-What's up, motherfucker?
-Boys...
-Hey.
So, we'll do men's
short-form figure skating?
My buddy Joe is in that
program. We trained together.
Would you guys be cool
to do that?
I'd love to show up for him.
Hell yeah, man.
Show up for any dude
who's that brave.
What do you mean?
Well, I'm assuming
your buddy might be gay.
I mean...
Fucking brave for a dude
to show up to this place
"Hey, here's me."
Russia is not safe
for folks like that.
Fucking balls of steel, man.
Yeah.
Welcome back to
Man in the Crease,
your one-stop hockey shop.
Today's first period topic
is the inevitable one
for the Admirals.
What has happened
to Scott Hunter?
70 points last season.
Yes, and we're 6 games
into this season.
A season he called
"need to win."
Those are his words.
And he has zero, zero points.
He's in a fog.
His passes aren't connecting.
He's barely skating.
I can't imagine he's amazing
in the room right now.
And he's already been announced
as Team USA captain
at the Olympics in Russia.
Um...
I am very sorry about that.
It's really not a big deal.
How may I help you?
Uh, what's, uh, what's good?
Um...
Just a bunch of
very decent smoothies
with deeply stupid names.
-Any allergies?
-No, no, no, I'm easy.
OK. I mean, the best one's
the blueberry one, but...
Oh, you mean
Blue Moon Over Brooklyn?
Yeah, that's it.
But what?
Oh, nothing.
Just when I make it for myself
in the morning, I add a banana.
Oh, so you're kind of wild.
I mean, it wouldn't be
the first time
somebody's told me that.
Uh, yeah, that actually
sounds pretty good.
Yeah?
Blueberry with a banana.
I'd take that, if it's OK
to order off menu, Kip.
Uh, I mean, technically,
it was my idea,
so I think we can
get away with it this time.
-Oh, you weren't kidding.
-It's really good.
Oh, yeah.
The banana makes
a big difference, I think.
Yeah...
I guess it must.
-Here.
-Thanks.
Um, that's way too much.
-It's for you.
-It's a great smoothie.
Thanks again, Kip.
Girl...
Holy shit! Are you...
Was that Scott Hunter?
Was that what?
Scott Hunter, the hockey player.
Girl!
Clock winding
down in the second period.
2-1 for Anaheim.
The Admirals...
And... this is what
we're watching?
We barely get to see you
'cause you're always working,
but at least when we do,
we get to watch, uh...
What is this?
Let me check my book. Hockey?
Shut up, Shawn.
Oh, so turn it off?
No, no, no, please keep it on.
-All right.
-Thank you, Kyle.
You're quite welcome.
Twice, he said "Kip."
Like, he used
your actual name twice.
Maria, that is
setting the bar so low.
It didn't even
sound stupid when he said it.
It almost sounded hot.
OK, that's not fair.
Not hot, just normal.
OK, I'm listening.
-Fuck both of you, OK?
-Kip is short for Christopher.
It's not that weird.
It's short bus for Christopher.
Please don't tell me you used it
on your grad school application.
Oh my God, why are we
talking about my dumb name?
-He said it!
-He said it.
Another round?
-Thank you, Kyle.
Hunter to Vaughn...
And you?
Thank you, Kyle.
-Oh, look, look, look!
-He's on the TV right now.
Shawn, look, right now.
Oh my God, OK.
Vaughn to Hunter.
Hunter is in front of the net.
And he scores!
A rare goal for Scott Hunter.
Oh, wow!
Right?
He knows your name.
Yeah. I mean,
he's definitely not gay, but...
-Shut the fuck up!
-He literally blushed!
-Then make him gay.
-Jesus Christ!
He scored
a hat trick last night.
Are you asking me
what that means,
or are you just telling me
something I already know?
I just didn't realize that...
We literally
watched the game, Kip.
Nice to see you again, Kip.
Nice to see you again, uh...
Scott.
-You're Scott Hunter, right?
-I am.
This is awesome.
I mean, wow, you
had a night last night.
Oh, did you watch?
I did, yeah. I don't usually.
Sorry, that sounds rude. I'm...
No, I get it.
Well, I watched the playoffs
last year with my dad.
It was amazing.
He's a huge fan.
But, yeah, I watched
last night. Wow.
Um, yeah, when something
goes right with my game,
I try to repeat it,
and then I try to perfect it.
OK.
So, I'd love
another smoothie, please.
Anything you'd like different?
Nothing at all.
There you go.
OK, you really
can't keep doing this.
I really can.
Uh, see you next game day,
I hope.
Dude.
-Girl.
-Was that...
Yes, it fucking was.
Sorry I'm late!
No outside food or drink.
Fuck off, Kyle.
And I know the whole smoothie
thing is dumb or whatever,
but he just keeps
saying my name,
and it's low key
making me crazy.
You're still coming to
that fundraiser, though, right?
I am not looking for a date.
Yes, I told you I could come,
and it's in, like, two months.
Could you please listen to me?
Kyle, remote!
Extra shrimp.
Thank you.
New York with control...
OK. Now I'm fully listening.
What are you doing?
Just putting the game on.
-Elena!
-What?
It's a sports bar.
Let's watch sport.
Am I being crazy?
What does Maria say?
She says he's
flirting with me too.
She is much smarter than you.
And probably this idiot.
The Admirals...
He's not an idiot.
Scott Hunter is...
Jesus!
Right?
When's his next home game?
-I don't know.
-Come on.
If you don't know when
his next game is,
how are you gonna
plan your shift?
I don't plan my shifts.
I just gobble up
as many as I can.
Saturday. They play
at home again on Saturday.
-Are you working?
-Um...
Fuck. No.
Fix that.
Kip!
Hey.
I didn't know if you, uh...
Well, it's...
it's nice to see you.
Uh, Blue Moon
Over Brooklyn, please.
Extra banana.
This one's on the house.
Oh, come on.
It's above my pay grade.
Management heard you came in.
And, no, you may not tip me.
And, yes, I'm using
proper grammar
to prove to you
that I'm being serious.
OK. Um...
Uh, may I drink this here?
I've got some emails
to answer, so I thought...
Yeah, you totally may.
You're not worried about
breaking your routine?
No, I'm not actually
that obsessive.
Turns out I'm too lazy
to be a serial killer.
I took a quiz.
I don't even think
I could be a spree killer.
What's a spree killer?
Someone who kills multiple
people at the same time.
But isn't...
A serial killer is someone
who kills multiple people,
minimum of three,
but over a period of time,
not all at once.
Mmm.
How do you know that?
I read a lot of murder books.
And, uh...
Yeah, serial killers
make me feel not obsessive,
which... which is a relief.
Well, I've read some things
about athletes.
OK, OK, before you say
anything else, yes, I agree.
And yes, there are at least
two guys on my team
that possibly off the record,
yes, maybe.
But no, not me.
No, I swear.
Barely had two concussions.
OK, so, what,
no left sock, right sock,
stop shaving, no sex,
all that stuff?
Oh, no, yeah, yeah, yeah,
all of that.
But that's not CTE stuff,
that's just science.
And science only really matters
during playoffs.
Oh, OK, that's super comforting.
I know you're
more of an art guy,
so it's not like I expect you to
get the ins and outs of science.
And just to be clear,
I'm not complaining
about the whole
stop shaving thing.
You all look like hot
lumberjacks by the end of May.
Uh...
Do you want to come
to my game tonight?
I have two seats.
No one's taking them.
So, I mean, if...
if you want.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I want.
Um... Fuck, man, that's crazy.
Thank you.
Super happy to do it.
You sure?
I'm sure.
These are better
than my company seats.
I get it.
These are really good seats.
Well, yeah, they're his.
You know, weird first date,
but I think I'm into this.
What are you talking about?
Well, you're with a girl,
and he's at work, so...
-Oh my God!
-Shut up, Elena.
Oh, wow!
-That wasn't...
-That wasn't to me. That was...
He just nodded at you.
No, there's no proof of that.
Wave back, for fuck's sake.
OK.
Good job, I love you.
I love you. I love you.
I love you.
Good job. I love you.
Hey, Hunter!
Too bad you can't play
at home every night, right?
It's better for you, huh?
Go fuck yourself, Rozanov!
It's more fun if you're there.
Hey, thanks!
Hope next time we play,
you decide to show up.
Cheap.
True.
You're starting
to sound like him.
I'm sorry, what?
You fucking heard me, Hollander.
What the fuck does that mean?
Well, there's something you
really don't expect to see.
Especially after
the final whistle.
And especially
from Hollander and Hunter.
A fittingly brutal end
to another brutal road trip
for the Admirals.
Has Shane Hollander
ever fought anybody?
Seem to have
some grievances to air out...
-I'm gonna hit the sack.
-Yeah.
Here you go, handsome.
All right, have a good day off.
It's not a day off. I'm doing
that catering thing tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah, just, you know,
you get to sleep in for once.
So I'm just happy for you.
That's all I meant.
You know.
I, uh, I'm proud
of your hustle, kiddo.
You know?
And you're gonna
get that scholarship!
Please, please, no jinxing me.
No way, no way. Good night.
Good night, Dad. Love you.
Love you back!
Motherfucker!
What's happening to you?
What's your problem?
I can't find my black suit,
and I have to leave so, so soon.
OK, well, it's with
the dry cleaning in my closet,
so why are you freaking out?
OK, hey, hey, are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine. I just...
I need the money,
and I can't fuck this job up.
Yes, and I get it,
but you're not gonna fuck it up
'cause you're amazing,
and it's gonna be great.
I love you!
Yeah, you too.
Yes, buddy!
I am so sorry.
Save it.
Motherfucker!
For God's sake!
-I'm so sorry about that.
-I'm really sorry.
Oh, you're a mess.
It's OK. It's not my only tux.
New York used to have
professional waiters.
Now it's models
who can't carry a tray.
It's, uh, it's really OK.
I'm so sorry again.
Oh, bunny.
Babe, I don't know
what that was...
I know, I'm a complete
fuck-up, and I'm sorry.
You're not a complete fuck-up.
This is not rocket science
or whatever it is you're into.
Art. Shawn,
please don't fire me.
No one is firing you.
Just calm down
and get your shit together. OK?
OK.
I know you need the money, baby.
-Yeah.
-OK?
Deep breath.
Inhale.
Exhale.
You think you can handle quiche?
They're dry.
And two.
Hey.
Hey, I am so sorry
about earlier.
That woman is horrible,
and I'm the one
who should apologize.
I was in front of
the door like an idiot.
No, I'm the idiot.
You're just a normal,
hungry person
at a fundraiser.
And that woman
did seem horrible.
I hate this food.
Well, full disclosure,
I hate serving it.
I'm sorry, I have to...
Do you like Mexican food?
Yeah, of course,
I'm not a serial killer.
Or even a spree killer.
You sure?
Yeah, who has the time?
Do you have the time
to grab a bite with me
when this thing is over?
Tonight?
Yeah.
With you?
Uh, well, yeah.
Uh, OK. Yeah, yeah.
'Cause there's, uh,
this great place
right around the corner,
and it's open late and...
OK. You don't mind
waiting until I'm done?
Not even a little.
-Hi.
Oh! That's a long line.
Is it worth it?
Um...
Probably not, right?
We also don't actually
have to do this.
How would you feel
about ordering in?
Holy shit!
Oh my God.
Wow.
I mean, I... I figured
you'd have a nice place,
but this is insane.
Do you want
the full tour now, or...
Or.
I pick or.
Wow. Wow,
you are so beautiful.
I can't believe
you're even into me.
I'm so into you.
So into you.
I can't stop thinking about you.
Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Oh my God!
What are you doing?
I didn't want to wake you.
And I just thought since
you have your game tomorrow,
and, you know...
Can you stay?
Yeah.
Then stay, please.
OK.
Did I wake you?
Ah...
OK, I meant to surprise you,
and I was gonna
go out and get stuff,
but I looked in your fridge,
and you basically
had all the ingredients.
I know I shouldn't be
snooping around,
but I didn't have to do
that much snooping.
You are very organized.
And I thought,
since I'm not working today,
but you still have your game,
that you probably
still want your...
Can I fuck you?
Absolutely.
So...
I should probably go.
Hmm.
Um, what if you didn't?
-Go?
-Yeah.
Like, ever?
Fuck!
All that serial killer talk
was you warning me, wasn't it?
Um...
I'm, uh...
I'm gonna say
a bunch of things, OK?
And I know I'm too intense,
everyone tells me that,
but I just...
I can't help it.
Is that OK?
Can I be too intense?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I, um...
I never do this.
Never brought anyone back here.
Like, ever.
Um, yeah.
My life is, uh, is complicated.
Yeah, I... I get that.
And I can't, um...
come out, like...
Not... not right now.
Too many people depend on me
for too much,
and it would just...
it would fuck everything up.
And so I just thought
I would, um,
I don't know, wait, I guess.
Yeah, wait till hockey was over,
and then maybe
I could fade away a bit or...
But I, um...
You, it's just, um...
I want you so bad.
So bad.
And I know that
you barely know me,
so why would you
even consider something
this probably fucked up?
Like, I... I know
I'm fucked up. I get it.
I'm not pretending I'm not.
But I really, really like you.
And I want you to stay.
So I'm asking for what I want.
I want you to be here when
I get back from practice later.
And I, uh, want you to be here
when I come home
from my game tonight.
I, um...
I want you more than I've wanted
anything in a long time.
Is, uh, is that too much?
You can say it if it is. Um...
Do say something, though.
I think I'd love to be here
when you get back.
And I don't think you're
too lazy to be a serial killer.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Yeah, you're definitely
not lazy.
Hey.
How was practice?
I don't know,
like, a few days ago?
Yes, I sent in the applications.
Yes, and even to BU.
And, yes, I know we hate Boston.
With Elena, Dad.
I'm staying with Elena.
So I don't have to
schlep to work.
I get to sleep in an extra hour.
Fuck yes!
Nothing, Dad.
No, I'm just watching the game.
Yes, with Elena, oh my God, Dad.
Where has she even been?
-Oh, please!
-I saw you three days ago.
Single since forever.
Overworked like she has
two wicked stepsisters.
Then she gets a man
and vanishes. What a cliché.
I don't have a man.
Hey, kid.
Keep the boyfriend on TV
at all times, please, Kyle.
-Oh my God, guys!
-He's a customer.
-He's not my boyfriend.
-Boo!
I don't have
a fucking boyfriend.
Oh.
Hi there.
Morning, Scott.
-Morning, Kip.
-The usual, please.
Yeah.
Extra banana.
Not sure what I'll do
without these on my trip.
I'm sure they have smoothies
in other cities.
Not like these, they don't.
Do you really think
this is a secret?
What's a secret?
Nothing's happening.
He's just flirting with me
or whatever.
He's straight, I think.
Girl...
Uh, there's pasta salad
in the fridge.
Chicken, no feta.
Oh yeah? From where?
From me. I made it.
You did?
Mm-hmm.
I'm not just a pretty face.
Oh, but you're
a very pretty face.
What's that?
It's an artist I love.
He has a new show out.
-Oh, cool.
-Mm-hmm.
I should buy some art.
What?
Hey, I'm not just
a pretty face either.
No, no, no, no.
You're also
a very, very hot body.
Hey!
We don't have to do this.
It's cool.
OK.
This would look great
in the living room.
Not on the fireplace wall,
but on the way to the bedroom.
-I think it would...
-Shhh!
Sorry. Sorry, I just...
-It's OK.
-Um, maybe we should...
Amazing, isn't it?
Yeah, it's beautiful.
So, are you two just browsing
or shopping to buy?
Oh, I think we're...
Yeah, I think we're just
browsing right now. Yeah.
-Thank you, though.
-Excuse me.
Sorry, he's not feeling well.
No problem.
I'm, uh, I'm really sorry.
I thought I could do that.
I really thought I could.
I wanted to. I just...
It's OK.
No, it's not.
I know it's not.
Come here. Come here.
These road trips
are just killing me.
I mean, it's brutal.
I think I'm cursed.
Cursed?
Like, scary old lady cursed?
I know. I know it's dumb.
But I'm not the only one
who's superstitious.
Would you be jealous
if I got my smoothies
from some other guy?
Maybe. Probably.
Well, what if I filled you in
on all the juicy details?
Like, how he blended them?
What if it actually
was a scary old lady?
Or what if you always
kind of had one with you?
What do you mean?
Ah.
Here.
-OK, I know it's dumb.
-I know it's dumb.
But I saw them at a bodega,
and I thought they looked like
your smoothie.
-I love them.
-Yeah?
I love them so much.
Can I fuck you?
Absolutely.
Fuck yes!
That's two tonight.
Can we say it out loud?
Is the curse broken?
Hunter hasn't scored twice in
an away game since last season.
What?
Say it out loud.
Say what?
Ah, OK, it's not...
It's what?
-OK, here's what I know.
-Elena...
Shut up,
you're in love with him.
I'm not in love with him.
You are.
Have you at least told your dad?
For how long now?
A little over two months.
Oh, baby.
Elena, hey,
you... you can't tell.
-If anyone finds out that it...
-That it's Scott?
Obviously, I'm not gonna
tell anyone, but Kip...
He can't come out right now, OK?
He really wants to.
It's amazing. He's amazing.
And I've never been happier.
Honestly.
What's the plan, babe?
-I don't...
-I don't know.
What does your dad think?
That I'm fucking some
married guy, probably.
Kind of wish you were.
Ah. Just don't
say that, please.
Just please be happy for me.
I can't wait to see you
in a tux tomorrow night.
I am gonna be super
well behaved for you.
I only care
that you're handsome.
You bitch.
Scott's gonna be there
tomorrow night too.
Oh, I know.
And he better be ready for me.
Hey, Dad.
-Oh my God!
-You're not dead!
No, I'm alive.
Well, that is a relief.
I didn't want to
have to call the morgue.
You know, I miss you.
I miss you too, Dad.
-All right.
-Yeah.
You gonna be
making an appearance here
at some point
in the near future?
Yes, I will.
Um, I'm gonna come for
dinner this week, I promise.
Perfect.
How's, uh, how's work?
Well, work is fine. You know,
Barry's being a pain in my ass.
Well, Barry's an asshole.
No, he hurt his foot.
So at least there's
something new this time.
Yeah, well, Barry's
always been an asshole.
Who taught you
to talk like that?
You did. You taught me
to talk like that.
That sounds about right.
And, uh, nothing
in the mail, right?
Kip, if there was something
in the mail,
I would not have
forgotten about it.
-I know, I know.
-I just figured I'd check.
OK. Don't worry about that.
OK.
Don't think about that, OK?
It's gonna come when it comes.
Look, I'm not gonna keep you.
I love you.
All right. You too, Dad.
You too, Dad, what?
I love you too, Dad.
There, I said it.
Oh my God.
-Sorry it's such a struggle.
-OK.
-OK, bye!
-Bye-bye!
Stop it.
Stop what?
He's here.
You need to chill out.
My God!
Can I have some of yours?
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
Well, I like our
playoff chances this year.
I think we might even get
some home ice advantage.
Well, if this guy
keeps playing
the way he has been, maybe.
What changed?
You meet a nice girl
or something?
I think we just found
our groove as a team.
-Excuse me, gentlemen.
-I think I spotted an old friend.
I'm just ribbing you, Scott.
You know your parents would
be so proud of you, right?
Your mom especially.
She would have
just been thrilled.
Thanks, Tom. Thanks.
-Excuse me.
-Yeah.
Hey. You OK?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I should be used to it.
Kip, right?
Christopher
when he's all dressed up.
I'm Elena.
-Nice to meet you, Elena.
-I'm Scott.
Pleasure, Scott.
-You look beautiful.
-You both do.
Uh, sorry.
Yeah, we both
clean up pretty well.
OK, if I go get more drinks,
do you promise to
start talking, Christopher?
-Of course.
-Great.
Another beer, Scott?
That'd be lovely, thank you.
Are you enjoying the evening?
I am. Are you?
Looking forward to
the after party, honestly.
Tux fits perfectly.
Thanks.
And thanks.
I mean, you didn't have to.
I wanted to.
You OK?
Elena knows.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Yeah, kind of got that.
It's, uh, it's OK.
She's, uh,
she's discreet, right?
Yeah, totally, totally.
I just, I, she kind of
figured it out,
and I guess
I had to tell someone.
It's OK. Really.
This is so weird.
Yeah. We should leave early,
as soon as I do my speech.
Uh, not before
you dance with me.
Pardon?
I wanna dance.
Elena's a killer.
How could I possibly say no?
So?
What are your intentions
with my Kip?
I'm serious.
He's crazy about you.
I'm crazy about him too.
I really am.
He's also miserable.
Are you miserable too?
No.
Wait, what do you mean?
Nobody wants to be
kept a secret.
-He's not a...
-He is.
Eyes on me, handsome.
I'm doing my best.
I... I love him.
I just can't do
better right now.
-I've been honest.
-I know.
And he's so in love with you
that he'll put up with it.
But it's killing him.
I'm not saying any of this
to be mean, I'm really not.
And you seem great.
But he's great too.
He deserves the best.
He deserves sunshine.
And so do you.
It's my birthday on Sunday.
I know.
I've already got
the caterer lined up.
-Surf and turf.
-Because we're not choosing.
You know The Kingfisher?
It's the bar I told you about
where I watch all your games.
Mm-hmm.
A couple of my friends
are throwing me just, like,
a little party there.
It's not even really a party.
It's just hanging out
or whatever.
Right.
It's a... it's a gay bar,
but it's not a club,
it's just a bar.
It's honestly more of a
hockey bar now, thanks to me.
Kip...
And I was thinking that you
could just come as my friend,
as somebody who
buys smoothies from me.
I mean, Maria knows,
my friend Sean knows.
They know that you buy
smoothies from me.
I can't.
I can't do that.
I wish I could.
I... I want to.
I want to tell everyone.
I want people to know
you're mine, that I love you.
I love you too.
Soon, maybe.
In a few years.
No, I know,
I know how it sounds.
But it'll go by quickly,
I promise.
And then we can be normal,
like... like other people.
I heard what you said
in your speech tonight.
And I know that
they're your family
and that you feel
responsible for them,
and I get that, Scott.
I really, really
get that, but...
I have a family too.
And I keep lying to them,
and I don't want to.
And I miss them.
I miss my dad.
Sorry, that's not what I meant.
-It's OK.
-I know what you meant.
I'm gonna go home tonight.
I need to.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
For those of you
who've attended before,
feel free to ignore my sob story
and go straight to the bar.
But for those of you
who don't know it,
here's the short version.
My parents were both
junior hockey coaches,
and they were hit
by a drunk driver
when I was 12 years old.
Mercifully for them,
they died instantly.
Mercifully for me,
the St. Thomas
scholarships existed.
I didn't have
anybody else to help me.
I had a lot of memories,
a love of hockey
and a huge hole in my heart.
St. Thomas filled it with hope,
the hope of a new family.
Things weren't always easy.
You know, they never are
for anybody.
But in hockey,
I found what I was missing,
first at my high school,
then later at college,
and now here with the Admirals.
And I never looked back
because I... I never had to.
The family I craved,
the family that I needed,
that I still need today...
hockey gave it to me.
And St. Thomas gave me hockey.
So from the bottom of my heart,
I want to thank you all
for being here tonight
and for supporting this cause,
because it's not just
a scholarship, it's...
It's everything
that comes with it.
It's a whole world,
a whole life.
It's...
It's everything.
Kip!
Hey, Dad.
-Hey, buddy.
-The prodigal son returned home.
Look, I got some mail here
for a certain someone,
and it's pretty heavy.
I want...
Hey...
Hey.
My boy.
Come here. What's up?
Whoa.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
For what? You got nothing
to be sorry for, silly.
Oh...
Hey...
OK, OK, here we go!
-Oh!
-Happy...
No, wait! No, wait!
Here's to turning 26,
and a full fucking ride
to grad school!
Yeah!
♪ What's the price
of being young? ♪
Hey, get dressed, man.
It's the gold medal
fucking game.
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
♪ What's the price
of being young? ♪
♪ Tie me up for dark love ♪
♪ Shiver down my empty spine ♪
♪ What's the price
of being young? ♪
♪ I think her lips
are close to mine ♪
♪ Her eyes are loosely gone ♪
♪ Painted nails
have fallen off ♪
♪ I think her lips
are close to mine ♪
Closed Captions: MELS